Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Constituent correspondence and services, Circa 1985-1990; Series 1
  - Rutenberg, Charles, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Rutledge, Cornelia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Ryan, Millie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sachs, Steven, 1988; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Safavian, Morteza, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Satterfield, Terry, 1989; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Sahlaney, Lee Anne, 1988; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - St. Clair, Bertha, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sager, Douglas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sanford, Gaynell, 1988; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Sanford, Jonathan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Sanz, Eva, 1990; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sanfran, Joe, 1988; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Savis, Evelyn, 1989; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Sayles, Brenda, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Schroffel, Steve, 1984; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Schwadron, Steven, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Schwat, Steven, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Schultz, Lawrence, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Scher, Barry, 1990; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Schlaifer, Emma, 1990; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Schlein, David, 1983; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Schneider, Matthild, 1986; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Schnipper, Harry, 1990; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Scott, Cynthia, 1990; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Scott, Elizabeth, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Scott, Pamela, 1989; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Scurlock, Robert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Seals, Melvin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Seiden, Louis, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Segal, Sheryl, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sellers, Steve, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Sellows, Stephen, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Seltzer, Richard, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Seward, Michele, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sexton, Eugenio, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Shafran, Joe, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Shalit, Anita, 1987; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Shannon, Terry, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Shapiro, Steven, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Shaw, Eugene, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Shaw, Margaret, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Shaw, Michel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Sharpe, Cynthia, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Scheeder, Donna, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sheehan, Elizabeth, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sheehy, Richard F., 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Shelton, Cardell, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Shelton, Cordell, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Shenton, Wayne, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sheppard, Janice, 1987; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sheridan, Wanda, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sherrill, Mildred, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Shiner, Whitney, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Shipman, Richard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Shuford, Verna, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sickles, Carlton R., 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Sidbury, Ellie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Silver, Jane, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Simmons, Dorothy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Simon, Robert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Simon, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Simons, Robert Jr., 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Simpson, James C., 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Simpson, Lenora, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Simpson, Steven, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Sims, Ralph, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Singh, Aquah, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Singletary, raymond, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Singleton, Anna, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Singleton, Earl, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Sizer, Venson, 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Slesinger, Larry H., 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Slocum, Derek E., 1987; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Smallwood, Jack, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Smith, Geneveive, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Sabrina, 1989; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Smith, Rosalee, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Smith, Robinson C., 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Smith, Raymond, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Smith, Marguerite, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Smith, Katherine H., 1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Smith, Jency, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Harold, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Smith, Sharon, 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Smith, Sterling, 1988; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Steeple, D., 1990; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Smith, Deidra, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Gladys, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Gail, 1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Frances, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Carmelida, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Elise, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Marguerite, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Geneva, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Sylvia, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Smith-Young, Grace, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Smoot, Bernice, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Smyth, David, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Snell, Stephen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Synder, Jennifer, 1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sobin, Dennis, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sowards, Evert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Snodgrass, Anne D., 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Synder, Denise, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Sparkman, Harry J., 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Speight, Willie Mae, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Spirer, Patricia, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Springer, A, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Stafford, Deborah, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Staley, Harold, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Stallings, Augustus G., 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Stalls, Richard, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Steele, Catherine, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Stein, Johanna, 1984; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Steiner, Monique, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Stevens, Douglas, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Stewart, Martha R., 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Stewart, Angela, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Stith, Don A., 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Stock, Tamara, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Stolline, Dean, 1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Stoner, Helen, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Stone, John, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Strand, Emilie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Stroube, Rosalie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Stuckey, Richard, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Sturdivant, Alberta, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Sturdivant, William, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Subon, Victoria, 1990; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Suber, Victoria, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Sullivan, Donald, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Sults, Ann, 1987; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Sullivan, Walter, 1986; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Sullivan, Charles, 1989; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Survey - Wage Increase and Residency Requiremnet for Metro Police, 1985; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Sutton, Percy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Swann, Vera A., 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Swedenberg, Jeff, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Swinton, Janet, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Swinton, JoAnn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Sypert, Henry, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Taft, William, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Talliaferro, Curtis, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Tanner, Barbara, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Tanner, Cynthia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Tate, Rolanda, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Alto, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Ann, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, James, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, Norris, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Taylor, Patricia, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, Robert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Taylor, Stanley, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Teitelbaum, G.A., 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Teffera, Elizabeth, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Terry, Charles, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - tenants of Frederick Douglas Apartments, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, Cecile, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Thomas, Lillian, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Thomas, Michael, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Thomas, Robert, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Thomas, Sammie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Thomas, Veeatrice V., 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Thompson, Chester, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Thorne, Carolyn, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Theus, Melvin A., 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Tillman, Wallace, 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Timberlake, Evelyn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Timberlake, Madeline G., 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Tingey, Bruce, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Tobias, Nichole, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Tollett, Erica, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Tolson, Mary, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Tomasso, Ronald, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Tomlinson, Paul, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Toomer, Timothy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Tower, John, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Townsend, Lewis, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Trammell, Sam, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Travers, Elizabeth, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Treacy, Vincent E., 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Trent, Anna, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Trent, Melvin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Trexler, Laura M., 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Trimmer, Lawrence, 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Trotter, Cherryl Y., 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Tucker, Andrea, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Tucker, Patricia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Turner, Carmen, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Turner, Denise, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Turner, Donna, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Turner, Gretchen, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Turner, Maurice, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Turner, Samella, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Turner, Sharon, 1988; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Turner, Vince, 1987; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Turner, Walter Mr. & Mrs., 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Tweedy, Anne, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Twice, Debra, 1989; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Umansky, David, 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Urban, David, 1990; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Vance, May, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Van Dam, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Van den Toorn, William, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Vanderwicker, Sarah, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Van derWood, Gerrard, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Varker, Diane, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Vermillion, Barry, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Wagoner, Shirley, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Waldron, Evelyn, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Walker, Julie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Walker, Karen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Walker, William P., 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Wallace, Rosalie, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Waller, Wilmer I., 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Walseth, Kristi, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Walsh, Paul, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Walstrom, David, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Walter, Pierce, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Walters, Mavis A., 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Walters, Richard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Walthorp, Clifton, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Ward, Ernest, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Ward, Michael, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Ward, Robert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Waschenko, Alexandra, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Washington, Andrew, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Washington, Andrew, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Washington, Elon, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Washington, Evelyn, 1985; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Washington, James, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Washington, Mamie, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Washington, Tharqurita, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Watkins, Pearl, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Watkins, Ralph, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Watkins, Vivian, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Webb, Isaiah, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Webb, Lorna, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Webb, Raychiel, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Wechter, Margaret, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Weddington, Beulah, 1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Wedgewood, OR, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Wells, Suzanne, 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Wemhoff, Daniel M., 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Werdel, Judith, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - West, Gladys, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - West, Ophelia D., 1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - West, Togo, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Westmoreland, Tim, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Whalen, Brian, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Wheatley, Katherine, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Wheeler, Phyllis L., 1987; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Whitaker, Rosa, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - White, Alice, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - White, Andrew, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - White, Joyce, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - White, Martha, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - White, Nayo, 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - White, Rhoda, 1988; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Whitehead, John, 1989; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Whittle, Elenor W., 1990; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Wicker, Addie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Wiggins, Wade, 1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Wilder, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Wilkes, Michael, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Almedith, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Betty, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Diane, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Dorris, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Gaston, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Williams, James E., 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Larry, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Saundra B., 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Wylie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Williams, Janet, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Keith, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Marion, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Norman, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Williams, Richard C., 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Williams, Verna, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Williams, Shelore C., 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Willis, Quadruplets, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Willis, Victor, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Willis, Kristina, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Jacqueline, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, Benjamin, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Bill, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Wilson, Bob, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Wilson, Frank, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Wilson, Helen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Wilson, James, 1979; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Wilson, Jesse, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Wilson, Thelma, 1982; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Wilson-Young, Sandra, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Winberg, Carol, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Haythe, Winston, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Winter, Thomas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Winters, Lottie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Wisdom, Ina M., 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Wolf, Dick, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Womeldorf, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Wong, Ruth S., 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Wood, Anton, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Wood, Elizabeth, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Wood, Gladiola, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Wood, Mike, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Wood, William, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Woodson, Carter G., 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Woodson, Cynthia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Woodson, Walter N., 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Wooten, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Wooten, Margaret/Shelton, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Wray, William, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Wright, Gilbert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Wright, Jack, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Wright, William J. Jr., 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Wein, Evelyn M., 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Wynn, Karen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Yates, Rudolph H., 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Yehulah, Elder, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Yellen, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Young, Albert, 1989; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Young, Joanne, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Younger, Tonya, 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Zavos, Michele Ann, 1987; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Zein, Fatima M., 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Zimmerman, Richard G., 1986; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Zimmerman, Jacqueline, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Zvirblis, Barbara, 1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Government business and correspondence, 1982-1990; Series 2
  Organized into three subseries: Legislation, Correspondence with government or public agencies of the District of Columbia, and Correspondence and official business of government branches of the United States and DC governments.
  - Legislation, 1982-1990; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Act 6-135, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Amendment Forms, Undated; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Arts Relief Tax, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bill 6-10, 1985; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bill 6-84, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bill 7-44, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Bill 7-154, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bill 7-228, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bill 7-300, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Bill 7-378, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Bill 7-378, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Bill 7-535, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Bill 7-536, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Bill 7-612, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Bill 8-2, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Bill 8-2, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Bill 8-8, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Bill 8-10, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Bill 8-20, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Bill 8-25, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Bill 8-35, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Bill 8-74, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Bill 8-82, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Bill 8-87, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Bill 8-96, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Bill 8-106, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Bill 8-109, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Bill 8-137, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Bill 8-156, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Bill 8-169, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Bill 8-188, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Bill 8-189, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Bill 8-192, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Bill 8-204, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Bill 8-232, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Bill 8-257, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Bill 8-259, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Bill 8-264, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Bill 8-300, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Bill 8-311, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Bill 8-316, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Bill 8-357, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Bill 8-369, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Bill 8-369, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Bill 8-374, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Bill 8-375, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Bill 8-382, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Bill 8-401, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Bill 8-408, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Bill 8-409, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Bill 8-461, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Bill 8-468, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Bill 8-650, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Bill 8-654, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Bills Referred to Committee, 1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Bills that Became Law, 1987-1988; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Child Abuse Prevention Act of 1985, Bill 6-190, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - The Coalition for Passage of the Rape Protections Act, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Committee Bills Now Law, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Public Service, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Committee Work '87, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Comprehensive Plan, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Council Resolution PR 8-157 National Park Service-CSX Rail Right of Way Resolution of 1989, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Councilmember Winter, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - CPW Bills 1989, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Curfew Law Teenage Drivers, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Curfew, Legislation, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Act 6-278, Alcoholic Beverage Control Act Reform Amend. Emerg., 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - DC Elections Code of 1955 Amendment Act of 1987, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 13)